CHINTAN TRIVEDI

Sudbury, ON

Email: - chintantrivedi15@gmail.com

Phone: - +1 263 288 4996

Professional Summary

Energetic person with excellent experience in fast-paced environments. Clear communicator with team-orientedfocus and advanced skills to effectively work with staff. Qualified and hardworking with upto-date handling permit. To seek and maintain a part-time position that offers professional challenges utilizing interpersonal skills, excellent time management and problem-solving skills.

Skills and Abilities

- Management
- Detail-Oriented
- Collaboration and Teamwork
- Customer Service
- Communication & Customer relations
- Problem solving
- Team leading

Work Experience

Food Server | Bombay Mahal

April 2024 - July 2024 | Montreal, Quebec

in Bombay Mahal I was working as a food server and front desk management as a cashier. In which I have to take orders of customer and inform in kitchen and serve food to customer also handling Take out Orders and Cash Counter.

Senior Sales Consultant (Corporate Sales) | Volkswagen Vadodara.

November 2023 – January 2024 Vadodara, Gujarat, India

Working as a senior sales consultant in corporate sales department at Volkswagen Vadodara. In which I must visit different MNC Companies and take permission for Events and arrange events and provide special rewards & offers to employees.

Service Advisor | Speed Car Service

August 2022 – October 2023 | Vadodara, Gujarat, India

In Speed Car Service I was join as a technician after 8 Months Promoted as a Service Advisor and Working as a service advisor. While I'm working as a Technician, I must find problems in vehicles and do general service of the vehicle and solving problems of Engine and Transmission. And as a service advisor I have to attend customers and scheduling appointments for their vehicles and update about work required in the vehicle and also do final inspection of the vehicle after maintenance work.

Sales Consultant | Volkswagen Vadodara

March 2022 - August 2022 | Vadodara, Gujarat, India

Working as a car Sales Repetitive at Volkswagen Vadodara in which I have to attend customer and do need analysis of customer needs and according to stocks I have to convert themand provide best deals with some negotiation to the customers also maintain relations with customers for new leads and references.

Salesperson | MB Chemicals

October 2020 - March 2022 | Ahmedabad, Gujarat India

I am working as a Salesperson in which I have to visit industrial areas and schedule meetings with responsible authority and give them brief about our products and takes orders for chemicals and after that keep in touch with companies for following reviews and upcoming orders.

Languages

- English (Fluent)
- Hindi (Fluent)
- Gujarati (Mother Tongue)
- French (Basic Greetings)

Education

MOTIVE POWER TECHNICIAN-TRUCK AND COACH

Cambrian College

Year: September 2024

DIPLOMA IN AUTOMOBILE ENGINEERING (FIRST CLASS WITH DISTINCTION)

Parul University Vadodara, Gujarat, India.

[GUJARAT TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY(GTU) AFFILIATED] Gujarat, India.

Year: August 2016 To December 2019.

10TH SSC

GUJARAT SECONDARY & HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD,

New Heaven Vidyalaya, Vadodara, Gujarat, India.

Year: 2016

Availability: Part-Time